Love isn’t an escape, it’s a reason to keep going.
Preparation for the Next Life is a drama, romance film directed by Bing Liu.
Aishe, a Uyghur woman trained by her military father, migrates to New York City
where she finds herself laboring in Chinatown’s underground kitchens.
She fatefully encounters Skinner, a young American soldier who has
just returned from three tours in the Middle East.
While falling in love, they discover the possibility of a better life together
than the ones they believed they were destined to live alone.
Aishe, played by Sebiye Behtiyar.
Skinner, played by Fred Hechinger.
Munro, played by Landyn Lu.
Chen, played by Ella Rouwen Chen.
Jim, played by B. Todd Johnston.
Luis, played by Maxwell Almono.
Preparation for the Next Life is a 2025 American drama film
directed by Bing Liu, from a screenplay by Martyna Majok.
It is based upon the 2014 novel by Atticus Lish.
It stars Sebiye Behtiyar and Fred Hechinger.
It was released on September 5, 2025, by Amazon MGM Studios.
The film explores themes of new york city, based on novel or book,
undocumented immigrant, juvenile detention center.
The tone is emotional.